Contact

ajcnor@att.net

www.linkedin.com/in/alicia-james-bb3707b3 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Surgery
Healthcare Management
Healthcare

Languages

English

Certifications

CNOR (Certified Nurse Operating Room)

Alicia James

StaRN Clinical Instructor - Perioperative Program Richmond, Texas

Summary

Experienced Clinical Instructor with a demonstrated history of working in the perioperative environment. Skilled in Perioperative Nursing, Healthcare Management, and Customer Service. Strong healthcare services professional with a Master of Science in Nursing focused in Nursing Education.

Experience

HealthTrust Workforce Solutions
StaRN Clinical Instructor - Perioperative Program
May 2018 - Present (2 years 1 month)

Ascend National Healthcare Staffing OR Circulator October 2015 - May 2018 (2 years 8 months) Houston, Texas Area

Memorial Hermann Surgery Center Southwest OR Clinical Manager August 2008 - October 2015 (7 years 3 months) Houston, Tx

Managing daily operations of the Operating room
Hiring/management of staff
Assists with supply/equipment management
Pharmacy management

Education

Prairie View A&M University

Master of Science in Nursing, Nursing Education · (2015 - 2018)

Southern University and Agricultural and Mechanical College at Baton Rouge

Bachelor's Degree, Registered Nursing/Registered Nurse · (1993 - 1999)